Guide to the Records of Religious and Benevolent Societies, Organizations, and Meetings
Yale University Divinity School Library
Records of Religious and Benevolent Societies, Organizations, and Meetings
1804-1987
RG 34
Yale University Divinity School Library
24
(58 boxes)
This collection contains publications of primarily American and British organizations, societies, conferences, and councils. The publications provide primary source documentation of organizations that focused on a wide variety of issues, ranging from sabbath observance to tract and Bible distribution to support of widows to religious education to ecumenical programs, etc.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
The publications in this collection date from the early 19th century to the 1980s.
Scope and Contents
Record Group 34 consists of primarily printed material. This guide lists the organizations and conferences alphabetically by name, with dates and place of origin also noted.
The religious and benevolent societies and organizations represented in this collection generally fit into one or more of the following categories:
Bible and tract societies
Christian education/ministry
Connecticut societies
Conferences, conventions
Ecumenical movements
Protestant Episcopal agencies
Related to Jews
Related to Roman Catholicism
Relief and charitable societies
Sabbath observance
Scholarly societies
Sects, religious societies
Societal reform
Published in the United Kingdom
Women's societies
Arrangement
The societies and organizations are listed alphabetically:
Bible -- Publication and distribution -- Societies, etc.; Charities; Christian education; Church charities; Church meetings; Church societies; Church work; Clergy conferences; Ecumenical movement; International relief; Jews; Learned institutions and societies; Religious gatherings; Sabbath; Sects; Social service; Tract societies; Women -- Societies and clubs; Great Britain -- Religion; Pamphlets; Fifield, James W., 1899-1977; Lee, Witness; American Bible Society; American Doctrinal Tract Society; American Revision Committee; American Sunday-School Union; American Tract Society; British and Foreign Bible Society; Brotherhood of the Kingdom; Catholic Church; Episcopal Church; Federation of American Zionists; Hibernian Bible Society (Dublin, Ireland); Interseminary Movement; Local Church; National Conference of Christians and Jews; New England Tract Society; Society for Promoting Christian Knowledge (Great Britain); Society for Promoting Due Observance of the Lord's Day; Spiritual Mobilization (Organization); Theosophical Society (Chennai, India); Unification Church; Universal Christian Council for Life and Work; Watch Tower Bible and Tract Society; Woman's Christian Temperance Union; World Conference on Faith and Order
- A
  - Academy of Parish Clergy, 1983 (Box 44)
    Scope and Contents
    Place of Publication: Cleveland, OH
    Subject Categories: Christian education/ministry
  - Albany Bible Society, 1817-1822 (Box 1)
    Place of Publication: Albany, NY
    Subject Categories: Bible and tract societies
  - Alliance of Unitarian and Other Liberal Christian Women, 1920 (Box 1)
    Place of Publication: Concord, NH
    Subject Categories: Women's societies
  - America Forward Movement, 1936 (Box 45)
    Place of Publication: Houston, TX
    Subject Categories: Miscellaneous
    Comments: Anti-communist movement
  - American and Foreign Bible Society, 1836-1882 (Box 46)
    Place of Publication: New York
    Comments: Includes Constitution, reports, 1836-1882; Paper re. Bible revision, 1850; Quarterly Papers, 1837-1841
  - American and Foreign Emigrant Protective and Employment Society, 1855 (Box 2)
    Subject Categories: Related to Roman Catholicism
  - American and Foreign Sabbath Union, 1846 (Box 28)
    Place of Publication: Boston
    Subject Categories: Sabbath observance
  - American and International Christian Moral Science Association (Box 28)
    Place of Publication: Philadelphia
    Subject Categories: Ecumenical movements; Societal reform
  - American Association for the Advancement of Atheism, c.1927, 1937 (Box 44)
  - American Bethel Society, 1838 (Box 28)
    Place of Publication: Buffalo, NY
    Subject Categories: Sabbath observance; Societal reform
  - American Bible Class Society, 1828 (Box 28)
  - American Bible Revision Committee, 1867-1897 (Box 20)
  - American Bible Society, 1816-1966, n.d. (Box 49–50)
  - American Bible Union, 1850-1854, 1869 (Box 1)
  - American Catholic Historical Society, 1892-1893 (Box 28)
  - American Christian Commission, 1867, 1869 (Box 28)
    Place of Publication: New York St. Louis
    Subject Categories: Ecumenical movements; Relief and charitable societies; Societal reform
  - American Church Literature Society, n.d. (Box 28)
    Place of Publication: Keene, NH
    Subject Categories: Bible and tract societies; Protestant Episcopal
  - American Church Union, c.1907 (Box 28)
    Place of Publication: unidentified
    Subject Categories: Protestant Episcopal
  - American Congress of Churches, 1884-1885 (Box 28)
    Place of Publication: Hartford
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies Ecumenical movements
  - American Doctrinal Tract Society, 1837-1853, n.d. (Box 1)
  - American Education Society, 1833, 1841 (Box 2)
  - American Humane Association, 1888 (Box 28)
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies
  - American Institute of Christianity, 1925 (Box 28)
  - American Institute of Sacred Literature, 1890-1891 (Box 28)
    Place of Publication: New Haven
    Subject Categories: Scholarly societies Connecticut societies
  - American Jewish Committee, 1938-1939 (Box 45)
    Subject Categories: Related to Jews
  - American Moral Reform Society, 1838 (Box 28)
  - American New Church Tract and Publication Society, 1883, n.d. (Box 28)
  - American New Testament Revision Company, 1880 (Box 51)
    Place of Publication:
    SEE ALSO: American Bible Revision Committee
  - American Protective Association, c.1893, n.d. (Box 44)
  - American Protestant Alliance, 1926 (Box 45)
    Subject Categories: Related to Roman Catholicism; Societal reform
  - American Protestant Society, 1843-1849 (Box 28)
  - American Revival Association, 1868 (Box 28)
  - American Sabbath Tract Society, 1865-1892, n.d. (Box 28)
    Subject Categories: Bible and tract societies; Sabbath observance
  - American Sabbath Tract Society (Seventh Day Baptists), 1934-1937, n.d. (Box 28)
    Place of Publication: Plainfield, NJ
  - American Sabbath Union, 1891-1892 (Box 29)
  - American Secular Union, 1889 (Box 44)
    Comments: re. Separation of church and state
  - American Society for Educating Pious Youth, 1816 (Box 2)
  - American Society for Promoting Christian Knowledge, 1846 (Box 45)
    Place of Publication: Charleston, SC
    Subject Categories: Christian education/ministry; Protestant Episcopal
  - American Society in Aid of The Evangelical Church of Italy, ca. 1894 (Box 2)
    Place of Publication: Brooklyn, NY
  - American Society of Church History, 1895, 1897 (Box 29)
    Subject Categories: Scholarly societies
  - American Sunday School Union, 1828-1944 (Box 2)
  - American Systematic Beneficence Society, 1856, n.d. (Box 29)
    Subject Categories: Relief and charitable societies
    SEE ALSO: Systematic Beneficence Society
  - American Tract Society, 1825-1935, n.d. (Box 3)
    Place of Publication: New York Boston
    Includes Annual reports of branch societies, 1825-1880; Christian Library - vols. 10, 11, 13, 25-28; Colportage reports 4: Evangelical Family Library - vols. 2, 7, 9-11, 13; Miscellaneous publications: (alphabetically by title)
  - American Tract Society (Box 4)
  - American Tract Society (Box 5)
  - American Union for the Relief and Improvement of the Colored Race, 1836 (Box 29)
  - Amitié Judéo-Chrétienne de France, 1980 (Box 44)
    Place of Publication: Paris
    Subject Categories: Ecumenical movements
  - Anglican and International Christian Moral Science Association, 1871 (Box 29)
    Place of Publication: London
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom
  - Anglo-Catholic Congress, 1927 (Box 29)
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom; Related to Roman Catholicism
  - Anti-Papal League, n.d. (Box 29)
    Place of Publication: Edinburgh
  - Anti-Sabbath Convention, 1848 (Box 29)
    Subject Categories: Conferences, conventions; Sabbath observance
  - Apostolic Faith Tracts, 1913 (Box 29)
    Place of Publication: Bloomsburg, PA
  - Appeal to Reason, n.d. (Box 29)
    Place of Publication: Girard, KS
  - Apples of Gold Library, 1898-1901 (Box 29)
    Place of Publication: Oakland, CA
  - Association for Discountenancing Vice and Promoting the Knowledge and Practice of the Christian Religion, 1835 (Box 29)
    Place of Publication: Dublin
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom; Christian education/ministry
  - Association for Promoting a Reform in the Ecclesiastical Provision for the Parish of Manchester, 1847 (Box 29)
    Place of Publication: Manchester, UK
  - Association for the Refutation and Suppression of Blasphemy and Sedition (Box 29)
    Place of Publication: Birmingham, UK
  - Association of Church Social Workers, 1944-1945 (Box 6)
    Place of Publication: Chicago
  - Association of Welsh Clergy in the West Riding of Yorkshire, 1852 (Box 29)
    Place of Publication: Carnarvon
  - Auxiliary Bible Society for the City and County of New Haven, 1817 (Box 47)
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies; Bible and tract societies
  - Auxiliary Bible Society of Montgomery County, 1819-1820 (Box 47)
    Place of Publication: Johnstown
  - Auxiliary Society for Promoting Good Morals, 1815 (Box 22)
    Place of Publication: Pittsfield, MA
    Subject Categories: Societal reform; Relief and charitable societies; Women's societies
  - Auxiliary Union of the City of Boston for Promoting Observance of the Christian Sabbath, 1828 (Box 29)
- B
  - Bahá'í­ Movement, 1914, 1936, 1946, n.d. (Box 29)
    Place of Publication: Chicago; New York; Wilmette, IL
    Subject Categories: Sects, religious societies
  - Baptist Congress for the Discussion of Current Questions, 1890, 1892 (Box 29)
  - Baptist Home Society of the City of New York, 1890-1899 (Box 29)
  - Baptist Tract and Book Society, 1870-1889, n.d. (Box 29)
    Subject Categories: Bible and tract societies; United Kingdom
  - Baptist Union of Great Britain and Ireland, 1848 (Box 29)
  - Benevolent Association of Windham County, 1850 (Box 22)
    Place of Publication: Windham Co., CT
    Subject Categories: Relief and charitable societies; Connecticut societies
  - Benevolent Association of the Church of the Holy Trinity, 1852-1857 (Box 30)
    Subject Categories: Relief and charitable societies; Protestant Episcopal
  - Benevolent Association of the County of Hampden, 1843-1855 (Box 6)
    Place of Publication: Hampden Co., MA
  - Benevolent Fraternity of Churches, 1835-1888 (Box 6)
  - Benevolent Societies of Franklin County, 1848 (Box 30)
    Place of Publication: Franklin Co., MA
  - Bibelgesellschaft zu Osnabrück, 1817 (Box 48)
    Place of Publication: Osnabrück
  - Bibelgesellschaft zu Wittenberg, 1823 (Box 48)
    Place of Publication: Wittenberg
  - Bible Reading and Prayer Alliance, 1887 (Box 43)
  - Bible Society in the County of Middlesex, 1819-1820 (Box 47)
    Place of Publication: Massachusetts
  - Bible Society of Massachusetts, 1809 (Box 47)
  - Bible Society of Middlesex County, 1846 (Box 47)
  - Bible Society of Philadelphia, 1830 (Box 51)
  - Bible Society of Saratoga County, 1818 (Box 6)
  - Bible Society of Washington City, 1844 (Box 51)
    Place of Publication: Washington, D.C.
  - Bible Students' Library, 1889-1903 (Box 30)
  - Bible Translation Society, 1840 (Box 30)
  - Bible and Prayer Union, 1888, 1892 (Box 30)
  - Biblical Society of New Haven, n.d. (Box 30)
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies; Scholarly societies
  - Bishop White Prayer Book Society, 1840-1899 (Box 6)
  - Book Society for Promoting Religious Knowledge Among the Poor, 1830, 1853 (Box 30)
  - Boston Young Men's Christian Union, 1852-1915 (Box 30)
  - Brighton Protestant Association, 1856 (Box 54)
    Place of Publication: Brighton, U.K.
  - Brighton Protestant Defence Committee, c.1840s (Box 30)
    Place of Publication: Brighton, UK
  - British Anti-state-church Association, 1845-1851, n.d. (Box 30)
  - British Reformation Society, 1829, 1852 (Box 30)
  - British Society for Promoting the Religious Principles of the Reformation, 1830, 1838, n.d. (Box 30)
    Place of Publication: London Birmingham
  - British and Foreign School Society, 1830-1841 (Box 6)
  - British and Foreign Society for Promoting the Colonisation of the Holy Land (Box 30)
  - British and Foreign Unitarian Society, 1826-1833, n.d. (Box 30)
  - Brooklyn City Tract Society, 1838, 1848 (Box 30)
  - Brooklyn Union for Christian Work, 1873, 1881 (Box 30)
  - Brotherhood of St. Andrew, 1900-1905, n.d. (Box 31)
  - Brotherhood of the Kingdom, 1876-1915 (Box 19)
  - Buffalo City and Erie County Bible Society, 1926-1927 (Box 47)
    Place of Publication: Buffalo
- C
  - Calvary Industrial Home, 1895-1896, n.d. (Box 21)
    Place of Publication: New Haven, CT
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies; Relief and charitable societies
  - Calvert Round Table of Boston, 1929 (Box 31)
    Subject Categories: Ecumenical movements; Related to Roman Catholicism; Related to Jews
  - Cambridge Camden Society, 1842-1846 (Box 6)
    Place of Publication: Cambridge, U.K.
  - Canterbury and York Society, 1905 (Box 31)
  - Carlow Bible Society, 1824 (Box 47)
    Place of Publication: Carlow, Ireland
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom; Bible and tract societies
  - Catholic Association, 1928 (Box 31)
  - Catholic Club of the City of New York, 1927 (Box 45)
  - Catholic Institute of Great Britain, 1839-1940, n.d. (Box 31)
  - Catholic Literature Society, 1940 (Box 31)
    Place of Publication: Los Angeles
    Subject Categories: Related to Roman Catholicism; Bible and tract societies
  - Catholic Record Society, 1929 (Box 36)
    Place of Publication: United Kingdom
  - Catholic Tract Society, 1843 (Box 31)
    Place of Publication: Baltimore
  - Catholic Truth Society, 1941, n.d. (Box 31)
    Subject Categories: Related to Roman Catholicism; United Kingdom
  - Central Bureau for Relief of the Evangelical Churches of Europe, 1933-1934 (Box 31)
    Place of Publication: Geneva New York
  - Central Committee for Protecting and Perpetuating the Separation of Church and State, 1885-1886 (Box 31)
  - Central Office for Evangelical Relief Work in Europe, 1923 (Box 31)
    Place of Publication: Zurich
  - Central Protestant Defence Association, 1868 (Box 6)
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom Related to Roman Catholicism
  - Chaplains' Aid Association, c.1917 (Box 31)
  - Charity Organization Society of the City of New York, 1909 (Box 7)
  - Chicago Tract Society, 1906-1913 (Box 7)
  - Children's Bible Union, 1885 (Box 31)
  - Children's Sabbath School Meeting, 1858 Jun 3 (Box 24)
    Place of Publication: New Haven (?)
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies; Christian education/ministry; Conferences, conventions
  - Christian Alliance, 1843, 1846, 1863 (Box 7)
  - Christian Amendment Movement (Box 45)
    Place of Publication: Topeka, Kansas
  - Christian Commission for Camp and Defense Communities, 1942-1943 (Box 46)
    Subject Categories: Christian education/ministry Ecumenical movements
  - Christian Commission on Wartime Campus Missions, n.d. (Box 46)
    Subject Categories: Christian education/ministry; Ecumenical movements
  - Christian Commonwealth Publishing Company, n.d. (Box 31)
  - Christian Cooperative Fellowship in North America, 1936 (Box 7)
    Subject Categories: Societal reform
  - Christian Council on Palestine, 1945, n.d. (Box 45)
  - Christian Endeavor
    SEE: International Society of Christian Endeavor; Connecticut Christian Endeavor Union
  - Christian Endeavor - First Annual Reunion of the Nutmegs, 1897 Oct 29 (Box 24)
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies; Conferences, conventions
  - Christian Instruction Society, 1829 (Box 31)
  - Christian Kingdom Society, c.1893 (Box 31)
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom Ecumenical movements
  - Christian Publishing Company, c.1886 (Box 33)
    Place of Publication: St. Louis, MO
    Comments: re. Disciples of Christ
  - Christian Tract Society, 1828-1854, n.d. (Box 31)
  - Christian Unity Foundation, 1911 (Box 32)
    Comments: research paper re. Disciples of Christ
  - Christian Unity Society, 1864 (Box 32)
  - Christian Workers Union, n.d. (Box 32)
    Place of Publication: Framingham, MA
    Comments: re. Sister H. S. McPherson
  - Church Anti-Slavery Society, 1860 (Box 32)
  - Church Building Society, n.d. (Box 32)
  - Church Charity Foundation of Long Island, 1876, 1892 (Box 32)
    Subject Categories: Protestant Episcopal; Relief and charitable societies
  - Church Congress, c.1941 (Box 32)
  - Church Pastoral-Aid Society, 1836-1863 (Box 7)
  - Church Peace Union
    SEE: World Alliance for International Friendship Through the Churches
  - Church Penitentiary Association, 1856-1857 (Box 7)
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom; Relief and charitable societies
  - Church Reform Union, 1871 (Box 8)
  - Church Scholarship Society in the Diocese of Connecticut, 1827, 1831, 1903 (Box 32)
    Subject Categories: Protestant Episcopal; Connecticut societies
  - Church Society for College Work, 1935, n.d. (Box 32)
    Subject Categories: Protestant Episcopal; Christian education/ministry
  - Church of England Book Society, 1889 (Box 32)
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom Bible and tract societies
  - Church of England Book-Hawking Union, 1859 (Box 32)
  - Church of England Scripture Readers' Association, 1847, 1849 (Box 32)
  - Church of England Sunday School Institute, 1858 (Box 32)
  - Church of England Tract Society, 1815-1840 (Box 32)
    Place of Publication: Bristol
  - Church of God, 1927 (Box 32)
    Place of Publication: Anderson, Indiana
  - Church of God (Free-Thinking Christian), 1841 (Box 34)
  - Church of Scientology World Wide, 1977 (Box 46)
    Place of Publication: East Grinstead, Sussex, U.K.
  - Clerical Society of Brooklyn, New York, 1845 (Box 32)
  - Cleveland Bethel Union, 1874 (Box 32)
    Place of Publication: Cleveland
  - Cleveland Christian Endeavor Union, 1893 (Box 35)
  - Colonial Church and School Society, 1856 (Box 8)
  - Columbian Reading Union, c.1890 (Box 32)
  - Commission on Interracial Cooperation, c.1930, 1931, n.d. (Box 22)
    Place of Publication: Atlanta
  - Committee for Christian Workers in the United States and Canada, 1889 (Box 22)
  - Committee for Free Christian Enterprise, n.d. (Box 8)
    Place of Publication: Sharon, PA
  - Committee for Promoting the Better Observance of the Sabbath, 1858 (Box 32)
  - Committee for the Relief of the Waldenses, or Vaudois, of Piedmont, 1843 (Box 43)
  - Committee of One Hundred, 1888-1890 (Box 32)
  - Committee of the Established Church Society, n.d. (Box 34)
  - Committee of the United Ukrainian Orthodox Churches, 1938, n.d. (Box 32)
  - Committee on Christian World Education, 1923 (Box 22)
  - Committee on Church and State, 1906 (Box 32)
  - Common Prayer Book Society of Pennsylvania, 1818 (Box 33)
  - Community of St. John Baptist (Protestant Episcopal), 1923 (Box 33)
    Place of Publication: Ralston, NJ
  - Concerted Church Campaign, 1915-1916 (Box 24)
  - Conference on Christian Union, 1845 (Box 33)
    Place of Publication: Liverpool
    Subject Categories: United Kingdom; Ecumenical movements; Conferences, conventions
  - Confraternity of Unity, 1929 (Box 8)
    Subject Categories: Protestant Episcopal; Related to Roman Catholicism; Ecumenical movements
  - Connecticut Association of the New Jerusalem, 1879 (Box 33)
    Place of Publication: Connecticut
    Subject Categories: Sects, religious societies; Connecticut societies
  - Connecticut Baptist Education Society, 1828 (Box 8)
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies; Christian education/ministry
  - Connecticut Bible Society, 1856-1904, n.d. (Box 22)
  - Connecticut Christian Endeavor Union, 1886, 1889 (Box 33)
  - Connecticut Council of Churches, 1946-195-, n.d. (Box 21)
    Place of Publication: Middletown, CT
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies; Ecumenical movements
  - Connecticut Federation of Churches, 1901, 1918-1925, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Connecticut New Church Association, 1893-1902, n.d. (Box 33)
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies; Sects, religious societies
  - Connecticut Pastoral Union, 1855 (Box 33)
  - Connecticut Reserve Bible Society, 1815-1816, 1824, 1826 (Box 8)
    Place of Publication: Warren, Ohio
  - Connecticut Sabbath School Union, 1830-1831, n.d. (Box 33)
  - Connecticut Sunday School Association, 1922 (Box 8)
  - Connecticut Temperance Society, 1830 (Box 8)
    Place of Publication: Middletown
    Subject Categories: Connecticut societies; Societal reform
  - Convention of Baptist Social Unions, 1874 (Box 29)
    Subject Categories: Christian education/ministry; Conferences, conventions
  - Convention of Delegates of Moral Societies, 1820 Jan 12 (Box 24)
    Subject Categories: Societal reform; Conferences, conventions
  - Convention of Ministers and Representatives of the Evangelical Churches in the City of Brooklyn, 1866 Jun 28 (Box 33)
    Subject Categories: Ecumenical movements; Conferences, conventions
  - Convention of Reformed Churches, 1838 Oct 17 (Box 33)
    Place of Publication: Pittsburgh
    Subject Categories: Conferences, conventions
  - Convention of Sabbath School Teachers of Massachusetts, 1865 (Box 38)
  - Council for Co-operative Theosophic Propaganda, 1911 (Box 33)
  - Council of Jewish Women, 1908-1911 (Box 33)
    Subject Categories: Women's societies; Related to Jews
- D-G
  - Defence Committee of the British Catholic Association, n.d. (Box 33)
  - Derby Church of England Co-operative Society, 1838 (Box 33)
    Place of Publication: Derby
  - Doctrinal Book and Tract Society
    SEE: American Doctrinal Tract Society
  - Dorset Church Union, 1849 (Box 33)
  - East and North of Scotland Liberal Association, 1879 (Box 8)
  - Edinburgh Bible Society, 1825 (Box 47)
  - Edinburgh Unitarian Library and Tract Society (Box 33)
  - Edward W. Hazen Foundation, 1941 (Box 44)
    Place of Publication: Haddam, CT
  - Elim Foursquare Gospel Alliance, n.d. (Box 33)
  - English Congregational Chapel-Building Society, 1856-1857 (Box 33)
  - English Monthly Tract Society, 1845 (?), n.d. (Box 33)
  - Episcopal Female Tract Society, n.d. (Box 33)
    Subject Categories: Protestant Episcopal; Women's societies; Bible and tract societies
  - Episcopal Prayer Book and Tract Society, 1816 (Box 33)
    Subject Categories: Protestant Episcopal; Bible and tract societies
  - Episcopal Sunday School Union, 1847 (Box 33)
  - Episcopal Tract Society of Philadelphia, 1934 (Box 33)
  - Essex County Bible Society, 1896 (Box 47)
    Place of Publication: New Jersey
  - Evangelical Education Society of the Protestant Episcopal Church, 1936, n.d. (Box 34)
  - Evangelical Ministerial Association of Cincinnati, 1863 (Box 34)
    Place of Publication: Cincinnati
  - Evangelical Protestant Association, 1922 (Box 45)
  - Evangelical Social Bible Union, 1880 (Box 34)
    Subject Categories: Ecumenical movements; Christian education/ministry
  - Evangelical Voluntary Church Association, n.d. (Box 34)
  - Evangelistic Association of New England, 1888-1915 (Box 8)
  - Evangelistic Committee of New York City, 1911-1928 (Box 8)
  - Fairfield County Bible Society, 1824 (Box 47)
    Place of Publication: Bridgeport, CT
  - Federal Street Society for Benevolent Purposes, 1824-1825 (Box 8)
  - Federation of American Zionists, 1907, 1910 (Box 34)
  - Federation of Churches and Christian Organizations in New York City, 1907 (Box 34)